One more paratha is enough,
let's eat it, we have to go to school
[Music]
Hello
[Music] Come on come on
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Bhaiya what should I cook for dinner, Didi is
not picking up the phone
[Music]
What is she reducing the insurance
[Music] We will go to
school, ok Sharma ji's son has
opened a sweet shop
[Music] He has
invited both of us for the inauguration today
[Music]
After Papa's departure, we were left with nothing,
I didn't even know that
Papa had a life insurance policy,
but Supriya Didi got the claim settled so quickly
that today we are able to stand on our own feet,
Papa's dream was a shop
[Music]
Khushiyan Baati
[Music] does
not mean just earning money,
this is how you earn something from your insurance
[Music]